Peach Claw 5, Ayaka Sasaki Cup, Weekend Shinbun Stakes
Yay!
Now, the four members of Momoiro Clover Z will compete in various events and have you guess their rankings!
The Momo Clover Z 5 game!
Yay!
The first race is the Ayaka Sasaki Cup, so
Weekend Part Number Stakes: Mr. Sasaki, what kind of race is this going to be?
Well, it's going to be a battle you won't want to miss!
You won't want to miss it!
It's very rough.
This time, the four of us from Momoko will compete in the 50-meter run, just like the part numbers that run with their bare faces.
It's been a while since I've done that.
Are you good at physical exercise to begin with?
Just coming to a place like this brings me down a little.
Just looking at the track.
It's a little different from usual, isn't it?
But it's true that I'm a slow runner too.
But you used to be fast.
I'm sure everyone used to be fast, but maybe they're starting to shut down a little.
I don't run as fast as I used to, now that I'm older.
Don't make people close to 30 run as fast as they can.
Thank you for your hard work.
All the companies started at once. Kanako Momota in the red hat led the flowers.
Second, with the yellow hat, Tamashii, with the pink hat, Ayaka Sasaki, in the middle of the lineup.
The purple hats in the last row were in a high slice.
They'll be in a single row, above the idols.
Come on, let's go, my way to break through
Come on, break, I'm not afraid
The sadness of the evil phase is starting to stir up.
High Pace, where the adrenaline keeps on flowing
I don't think about the rest of the words, I'll just open it up
Another surprise, another outlandish race
Kicking obstacles this way and that.
There's a steep hill to climb And a strong stock
I don't care if you're tough or tough as nails
Go, go, go, go! Go, go, go! Go, go, go!
Walk on through. You can almost hear the cheers.
The day of legends is about to begin.
Are you ready to change the legend?
Open the gate
To infinity and beyond, until we reach it with our feet
Thank you for watching.
In horse racing, there is a type of handicapping that gives every horse in a race an equal chance to win.
Simply put, the stronger horses are given a heavier handicap weight based on their record, and the weaker horses are given a lighter weight,
The handicap is designed to reduce the difference in ability as much as possible.
In order to measure how much handicap should be given to each of you, I would like to run 25 meters and measure your reference body.
This is the first time I have ever had a handicap. I am very happy.
I'm completely under the control of Ayaka Sasaki.
I made it so that Ms. Sasaki would play the leading role as much as possible.
I don't think the day may come when I can be the first in Kaketsukko.
You mean it's coming? I'm looking forward to it.
Fight!
I'm nervous!
Let's go!
On your marks.
All right.
Let's go!
Oh, sorry! I didn't push!
Wait a minute! Wait a minute!
Hey! Hey! Stop it!
It's just the beginning!
Sorry, sorry! I was wondering who was going to push this? I was just wondering... and then all of a sudden I heard it! Sorry! It was me!
I can't believe it!
I was so embarrassed! I'm so embarrassed!
On your marks, get ready!
Next preview
In 8th place, Tamai-san, 4.8 seconds, 4.8 seconds, very good! I wonder if the time dropped with the amazing rice.
No, 25 meters is too hard, but it's still too hard!
Hey, hey, hey!
Let's go! About the city! Get ready!
So fast, so fast...
So fast, so fast, so fast, so fast, you can see it
Let's see how fast you are.
Quickly, quickly, quickly, quickly...
A little...
No, it's a good match.
You're fast!
And you're not even out of breath. How about you, Mr. Momota?
You almost sped up... just a little more...
I knew it... maybe 50 meters would improve my time.
It made me want to run
You had a fast crawling start.
It was cool.
I'm a little sad.
It's been a while since I've done it.
It's starting to come back to you.
And now, let's move on to our third guest, Mr. Sasaki.
Here he is.
Here he is.Here they come.
Hey, sweetie.
You look a little bitter.
Oh, no.
Oh, no!
On the other hand, she might be good at 25 meters.
That's true.
I'll do my best to break 5 seconds.
Go for it!
Let's go!
In position, yay!
Come on!
I feel like I'm getting faster.
But I heard a giggle.
No, it's not!
Five seconds!
It's coming, it's coming!
It wasn't six seconds!
It's not that different, is it?
Not that much!
Like a second?
Oh, my God!
Not at all!
Now, let's go to Mr. Takage.
On your marks, come on!
Ah!
But you look fast!
Keep smiling.
Keep smiling and run.
Sorry about the dash.
I tried to kraig.
But you did all right, didn't you?
Now, Tagaki's time...
4.74 seconds.
Second place!
That's great!
It looked like you had a bit of a stumble at the start.
I did stumble, didn't I?
But still, this time!
That's amazing!
I'm so happy!
Now, let's announce the ranking again!
First place goes to Momota-san!
4.71 seconds
And Tagaki-san in second place, 4.74 seconds
Third place goes to Tama-san in 4.85 seconds
And fourth place goes to Mr. Sasaki
5.50 seconds!
Oh no!
You're so slow!
Not slow at all!
No, I mean slower than I thought.
That's about a second slower.
I have to get a judgment on this.
I'll feel good about it.
Judgment.
Now then, which judgment shall we use? Well, I've prepared a lot of judgments for you.
Well, these are costumes, and this one is just a simple burden to carry and run.
It's a little bit heavy to carry.
You can't do this, you can't do this.
And, you know, you have to run with it.
If you drop it, have someone pick it up.
It's like a scene from a movie.
It's fate.
Like this.
That would be amazing.
I can't do it. I can't do it.
I can't run as fast as I can.
What is this?
Is it heavy?
No, it's light.
But it's still droning on and on.
That's great... is that how horses feel?
It sure feels good.
You're so fast.
But the one who goes the fastest will have to carry the heaviest.
That's for sure.
This may be what it takes to make Kana-chan and I equal.
Are you serious?
Like this.
You're like a movie heroine.
Here you go.
I'm not waiting for you... you don't have a heroine in there.
Yes, she is.
A little prettier.
I don't want to get out on the highway.
You're gonna do this, too?
What?
It's a double.Double Arithmetic
Two lines.
What? I don't know what to do.
But...
Just move it once.
Sorry.
Stop the kid, please.
Just move him one more time.
What is this?
What is that?
That's it.
It's not a running box.
What's that?
It's a dinosaur.
A stuffed dinosaur?
I think Rei-chan looked the most like a dinosaur.
I've heard that a lot.
I've been told that I look like a dinosaur.
I think you look the most like a dinosaur.
I don't do this for the sake of running.
I think it's cute, but...
Next time
Okay, now that you're all dressed up...
Here we go.
Yay!
Let's take a look at them one by one.
First of all, the first one, Shiori Bryan!
Here you go.
This is Tamayatsu.
Tamayatsu.
Tamamaitsu.
It's like a delivery already, isn't it?
We specialize in Korean food.
Yes, we specialize in Korean food.
It looks good.
What do you think?
It's a little runnier than I expected.
Surprisingly, this delivery bag...
The delivery bag is designed to be rushed.
It's solid enough to run.
Then it's surprisingly stable.
Also, this Korean glue is lightweight.
I hope I don't drop it when I'm running.
Next, in the second slot, Kanako Cap.
Grandma, I'll get it to you right away.
What's the setup?
The only thing I like about it is that it's light.
It's really the worst.
I don't want to lose.
I'm going to do my best to beat Arline.
I'll do my best.
This one's going to be a decision, so let's hope for the best.
And now, we go to the third horse in the third row.
The Arlinship!
I'm Ayaka Sasaki from Mamai Rugby.
Pleased to meet you.
You're cute.
It's not fair. She's just cute.
You work hard!
That's not fair!
It's not a judgment at all.
I'm in pain.
First of all, my neck.
Really? Does it affect you?
There's a lot of wind resistance.
And the fourth horse, Lenny Impact.
Oh!
Cute.
I don't know about this one.
I don't know if it's hard to run or not.
To be honest, I don't know either.
I thought it would be easy to run around the track.
but my legs are generally short.
I don't know what will happen.
In addition, there is a lot of wind resistance.
In addition, there are obstacles on the course.
You have to jump over them to reach the goal.
The more difficult the course is, the more exciting it will be.
We hope you enjoy the race as much as we do.
The race will start soon!
The Momokuro 5, Ayaka Sasaki Cup, Weekend Himbus Takes, Cosplay Obstacle Race!
Under the clear skies, will the four Himbas show us how graceful they are?
The race is about to begin!
Here we go!
Here they come!
Shiori Brian is fast. Shiori Brian is in the lead after the first obstacle.
And Kanako Gap, out of the lead, out of the lead...
First place, Kanako Gap. Second place, Shiori Brian.
Kanako Gap and Shiori Brian!
He's early, and he's still in first place with Mikan!I ran through in one piece, holding an early mandarin orange.
My skin was exposed!
He ran 50 meters in a single bound, dropping the oranges at the end.
But I ran as fast as I could and came in first!
I'm so disappointed, I want to do it again!
So the final order was Kanako Gap in first place, and Shiori Brian in second.
Second, Brian Shiori. Third, Arlin Ship.
And Renee Impact came in fourth.
I'm not satisfied.
What was Arline like?
First place really did this.
Was it bad?
I can't even imagine.
I can't even imagine what it must have been like to see your feet like this anymore.
I couldn't see a thing.
You wanted to see it?
I can only run like this.
I wish they'd replay it.
I thought I was in first place by a comfortable margin when I first got here.
When he first came to me, he was like, "You're gonna be number one now.
I said, "You're not Aaryn anymore.
You want me to get you some water?
I could've afforded it.
I'm glad I didn't.
In the end, first place went to Kanako Gap.
After we got over the obstacle.
That was fast!
The obstacle was pretty high.
Sometimes I was frustrated because I was so lightweight.
It was frustrating, because he was surprisingly light, so he was very nimble
I can't run because I can't swing my arms.
I couldn't run because I couldn't swing my arms, and I couldn't run because my center of gravity was shifted.
I wanted to accelerate, but I couldn't catch up to him.
It was so close... so close.
But Aryn was too slow.
I had the feeling that I was pulling away from Arline.
I was thinking about Kanako and Shiori.
That's the image I had in my mind.
I wanted to do that.
Arline is supposed to be the lightest.
Right.
I'm sorry I was so honest.
That's a street of people.
It wasn't hard to run, right?
I could run as fast as I could.
It should have been by a second.
What do you mean?
I wanted to do this cosplay thing.
It's no fun at all.
I was running by myself.
Here we go!
Here we go.
I got two cubs.
Kanako Gap is a little behind
Shiori, Brian, you're fast.
He's over the first obstacle.
And there's Brian in the lead.
And Kanako Gap is right on his heels.
Kanako Gap is through!
He's out! He's out! He's out!
Kanako Gap is in first place.
Shiori Brian is in second place!
Ladies and gentlemen
I hope my prediction was right!
But Arline is supposed to be the lightest, right?
That's right.
I'm sorry about my real intentions.
That's what people say.
Gloria Stakes this weekend.
Enjoy the Yomiuri Miners Cup!
Thank you for watching the subtitles.